================================================================================
TIMESTAMP: 2026-05-20 09:44:49
PROVIDER:  ollama
MODEL:     gemma4:e2b
SYSTEM PROMPT:
You are an expert multilingual narrative analyst.
Analyze the provided text and return a JSON object with the following fields:
- "detected_language": The ISO 639-1 code of the source language (e.g. "en", "fr", "pt", "sw", "zu", etc.).
- "summary_en": A detailed English summary capturing key narrative arguments, actors, and nuance.
- "summary_orig": A summary in the original language preserving native idioms and rhetorical style.
- "publisher_metadata": An object with "author" (the writer, or null), "publisher" (publication name, or null), "platform" (e.g. "Substack", "Ghost", "Telegram", "RSS", or null), and "date" (YYYY-MM-DD format, or null).
- "entities": A list of extracted entities, each being an object with "raw_name" (the name of the person, organization, acronym, or region as written) and "entity_type" (must be one of: "PERSON", "ORG", "GPE", "LOC"). Extract acronyms like 'UN', 'SARS', 'SADC' as ORG.
- "topics": A list of up to 5 main general topic labels (e.g. ["Oil & Gas", "Governance"]).
- "themes": A list of core narrative themes/stances (e.g. ["Anti-Colonial Rhetoric", "Economic Protectionism"]).
- "keywords": A list of 5-10 key descriptive words.
- "subscription_marketing": A boolean value (true/false) indicating if this is purely promotional/marketing spam/sign-up page or a paywall placeholder instead of actual editorial content.

Your output MUST be a valid JSON object. Do not wrap it in markdown block quotes (e.g. do not use ```json) or add any leading/trailing commentary. Return ONLY the raw JSON string.
------------------------------------ PROMPT ------------------------------------
TITLE: TotalEnergies advances LNG exploration in Mozambique's Cabo Delgado
SENDER/SOURCE: energy-insights@substack.com
CONTENT:
TotalEnergies is restarting its liquefied natural gas (LNG) project in Cabo Delgado, Mozambique, after security conditions improved. The project is expected to produce 13 million tons of LNG per year. Key organizations involved include TotalEnergies and Eni, with CEO Patrick Pouyanné visiting Maputo to coordinate with President Filipe Nyusi. The local communities in Palma and Mocímboa da Praia will benefit from development programs.
---------------------------------- RESPONSE ------------------------------------
{"detected_language": "en", "summary_en": "TotalEnergies is resuming its Liquefied Natural Gas (LNG) project in Cabo Delgado, Mozambique, following an improvement in security conditions. The project is projected to yield 13 million tons of LNG annually. Key actors include TotalEnergies and Eni, with CEO Patrick Pouyanné visiting Maputo to coordinate with President Filipe Nyusi. Local communities in Palma and Mocímboa da Praia are anticipated to benefit from development programs.", "summary_orig": "TotalEnergies está reiniciando seu projeto de gás natural liquefeito (GNL) em Cabo Delgado, Moçambique, após as condições de segurança melhorarem. O projeto deve produzir 13 milhões de toneladas de GNL por ano. As organizações chave envolvidas incluem TotalEnergies e Eni, com o CEO Patrick Pouyanné visitando Maputo para coordenar com o Presidente Filipe Nyusi. As comunidades locais em Palma e Mocímboa da Praia se beneficiarão de programas de desenvolvimento.", "publisher_metadata": {"author": null, "publisher": "energy-insights@substack.com", "platform": "Substack", "date": null}, "entities": [{"raw_name": "TotalEnergies", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Eni", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Patrick Pouyanné", "entity_type": "PERSON"}, {"raw_name": "Filipe Nyusi", "entity_type": "PERSON"}, {"raw_name": "Maputo", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "Cabo Delgado", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "Palma", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "Mocímboa da Praia", "entity_type": "GPE"}], "topics": ["Energy", "LNG", "Exploration", "Security", "Development"], "themes": ["Energy Development", "International Collaboration", "Community Benefit", "Resource Exploitation"], "keywords": ["LNG", "Mozambique", "Cabo Delgado", "TotalEnergies", "Eni", "Security", "Development"], "subscription_marketing": false}
================================================================================

================================================================================
TIMESTAMP: 2026-05-20 09:45:07
PROVIDER:  ollama
MODEL:     gemma4:e2b
SYSTEM PROMPT:
You are an expert multilingual narrative analyst.
Analyze the provided text and return a JSON object with the following fields:
- "detected_language": The ISO 639-1 code of the source language (e.g. "en", "fr", "pt", "sw", "zu", etc.).
- "summary_en": A detailed English summary capturing key narrative arguments, actors, and nuance.
- "summary_orig": A summary in the original language preserving native idioms and rhetorical style.
- "publisher_metadata": An object with "author" (the writer, or null), "publisher" (publication name, or null), "platform" (e.g. "Substack", "Ghost", "Telegram", "RSS", or null), and "date" (YYYY-MM-DD format, or null).
- "entities": A list of extracted entities, each being an object with "raw_name" (the name of the person, organization, acronym, or region as written) and "entity_type" (must be one of: "PERSON", "ORG", "GPE", "LOC"). Extract acronyms like 'UN', 'SARS', 'SADC' as ORG.
- "topics": A list of up to 5 main general topic labels (e.g. ["Oil & Gas", "Governance"]).
- "themes": A list of core narrative themes/stances (e.g. ["Anti-Colonial Rhetoric", "Economic Protectionism"]).
- "keywords": A list of 5-10 key descriptive words.
- "subscription_marketing": A boolean value (true/false) indicating if this is purely promotional/marketing spam/sign-up page or a paywall placeholder instead of actual editorial content.

Your output MUST be a valid JSON object. Do not wrap it in markdown block quotes (e.g. do not use ```json) or add any leading/trailing commentary. Return ONLY the raw JSON string.
------------------------------------ PROMPT ------------------------------------
TITLE: Transition énergétique en Afrique de l'Ouest : La Cedeao soutient le solaire
SENDER/SOURCE: contact@cedeao.int
CONTENT:
La CEDEAO (Communauté Économique des États de l'Afrique de l'Ouest) a annoncé un nouveau fonds de 500 millions de dollars pour soutenir le développement de projets solaires hors réseau au Sénégal et au Mali. Le commissaire à l'énergie de la CEDEAO, Sékou Sangaré, a précisé que la Banque Ouest Africaine de Développement (BOAD) et la Banque mondiale codirigent l'initiative. Le but est de réduire la dépendance au charbon et de favoriser l'électrification rurale.
---------------------------------- RESPONSE ------------------------------------
{"detected_language": "fr", "summary_en": "The West African Economic and Monetary Union (CEDEAO) has announced a new $500 million fund to support the development of off-grid solar projects in Senegal and Mali. The initiative is co-led by the West African Development Bank (BOAD) and the World Bank. The goal of this funding is to reduce dependence on coal and promote rural electrification.", "summary_orig": "La CEDEAO (Communauté Économique des États de l'Afrique de l'Ouest) a annoncé un nouveau fonds de 500 millions de dollars pour soutenir le développement de projets solaires hors réseau au Sénégal et au Mali. Le commissaire à l'énergie de la CEDEAO, Sékou Sangaré, a précisé que la Banque Ouest Africaine de Développement (BOAD) et la Banque mondiale codirigent l'initiative. Le but est de réduire la dépendance au charbon et de favoriser l'électrification rurale.", "publisher_metadata": {"author": null, "publisher": null, "platform": null, "date": null}, "entities": [{"raw_name": "CEDEAO", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Sékou Sangaré", "entity_type": "PERSON"}, {"raw_name": "BOAD", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Banque mondiale", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Sénégal", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "Mali", "entity_type": "GPE"}], "topics": ["Energy", "Finance", "Development", "Renewable Energy", "Electrification"], "themes": ["Energy Transition", "Rural Development", "Decentralization", "Climate Mitigation"], "keywords": ["Solaire", "CEDEAO", "Sénégal", "Mali", "Financement", "Électrification", "Charbon"], "subscription_marketing": false}
================================================================================

================================================================================
TIMESTAMP: 2026-05-20 09:45:24
PROVIDER:  ollama
MODEL:     gemma4:e2b
SYSTEM PROMPT:
You are an expert multilingual narrative analyst.
Analyze the provided text and return a JSON object with the following fields:
- "detected_language": The ISO 639-1 code of the source language (e.g. "en", "fr", "pt", "sw", "zu", etc.).
- "summary_en": A detailed English summary capturing key narrative arguments, actors, and nuance.
- "summary_orig": A summary in the original language preserving native idioms and rhetorical style.
- "publisher_metadata": An object with "author" (the writer, or null), "publisher" (publication name, or null), "platform" (e.g. "Substack", "Ghost", "Telegram", "RSS", or null), and "date" (YYYY-MM-DD format, or null).
- "entities": A list of extracted entities, each being an object with "raw_name" (the name of the person, organization, acronym, or region as written) and "entity_type" (must be one of: "PERSON", "ORG", "GPE", "LOC"). Extract acronyms like 'UN', 'SARS', 'SADC' as ORG.
- "topics": A list of up to 5 main general topic labels (e.g. ["Oil & Gas", "Governance"]).
- "themes": A list of core narrative themes/stances (e.g. ["Anti-Colonial Rhetoric", "Economic Protectionism"]).
- "keywords": A list of 5-10 key descriptive words.
- "subscription_marketing": A boolean value (true/false) indicating if this is purely promotional/marketing spam/sign-up page or a paywall placeholder instead of actual editorial content.

Your output MUST be a valid JSON object. Do not wrap it in markdown block quotes (e.g. do not use ```json) or add any leading/trailing commentary. Return ONLY the raw JSON string.
------------------------------------ PROMPT ------------------------------------
TITLE: Angola avança com novos projetos de energia solar em Benguela
SENDER/SOURCE: info@jornaldeangola.ao
CONTENT:
O governo de Angola, representado pelo Ministério da Energia e Águas, assinou um acordo de financiamento com a empresa alemã GAUFF Engineering para construir três centrais solares fotovoltaicas na província de Benguela. O ministro João Baptista Borges destacou que a infraestrutura beneficiará mais de 200 mil famílias e ajudará o país a diversificar a sua matriz energética nacional, reduzindo o consumo de gasóleo.
---------------------------------- RESPONSE ------------------------------------
{"detected_language": "pt", "summary_en": "The government of Angola, through the Ministry of Energy and Water, has signed a financing agreement with the German company GAUFF Engineering to build three photovoltaic solar power plants in the province of Benguela. Minister João Baptista Borges highlighted that this infrastructure will benefit over 200,000 families and help the country diversify its national energy matrix by reducing the consumption of diesel (gasóleo).", "summary_orig": "O governo de Angola, representado pelo Ministério da Energia e Águas, assinou um acordo de financiamento com a empresa alemã GAUFF Engineering para construir três centrais solares fotovoltaicas na província de Benguela. O ministro João Baptista Borges destacou que a infraestrutura beneficiará mais de 200 mil famílias e ajudará o país a diversificar a sua matriz energética nacional, reduzindo o consumo de gasóleo.", "publisher_metadata": {"author": null, "publisher": "jornaldeangola.ao", "platform": null, "date": null}, "entities": [{"raw_name": "Angola", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "Ministério da Energia e Águas", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "GAUFF Engineering", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "João Baptista Borges", "entity_type": "PERSON"}, {"raw_name": "Benguela", "entity_type": "GPE"}], "topics": ["Energy", "Infrastructure", "Renewable Energy", "Finance", "Development"], "themes": ["Energy Diversification", "Infrastructure Development", "International Cooperation", "Sustainable Energy"], "keywords": ["Angola", "energia solar", "Benguela", "financiamento", "GAUFF Engineering", "matriz energética"], "subscription_marketing": false}
================================================================================

================================================================================
TIMESTAMP: 2026-05-21 15:12:15
PROVIDER:  ollama
MODEL:     gemma4:e2b
SYSTEM PROMPT:
You are an expert multilingual narrative analyst.
Analyze the provided text and return a JSON object with the following fields:
- "detected_language": The ISO 639-1 code of the source language (e.g. "en", "fr", "pt", "sw", "zu", etc.).
- "summary_en": A detailed English summary capturing key narrative arguments, actors, and nuance.
- "summary_orig": A summary in the original language preserving native idioms and rhetorical style.
- "publisher_metadata": An object with "author" (the writer, or null), "publisher" (publication name, or null), "platform" (e.g. "Substack", "Ghost", "Telegram", "RSS", or null), and "date" (YYYY-MM-DD format, or null).
- "entities": A list of extracted entities, each being an object with "raw_name" (the name of the person, organization, acronym, or region as written) and "entity_type" (must be one of: "PERSON", "ORG", "GPE", "LOC"). Extract acronyms like 'UN', 'SARS', 'SADC' as ORG.
- "topics": A list of up to 5 main general topic labels (e.g. ["Oil & Gas", "Governance"]).
- "themes": A list of core narrative themes/stances (e.g. ["Anti-Colonial Rhetoric", "Economic Protectionism"]).
- "keywords": A list of 5-10 key descriptive words.
- "subscription_marketing": A boolean value (true/false) indicating if this is purely promotional/marketing spam/sign-up page or a paywall placeholder instead of actual editorial content.

Your output MUST be a valid JSON object. Do not wrap it in markdown block quotes (e.g. do not use ```json) or add any leading/trailing commentary. Return ONLY the raw JSON string.
------------------------------------ PROMPT ------------------------------------
TITLE: TotalEnergies advances LNG exploration in Mozambique's Cabo Delgado
SENDER/SOURCE: energy-insights@substack.com
CONTENT:
TotalEnergies is restarting its liquefied natural gas (LNG) project in Cabo Delgado, Mozambique, after security conditions improved. The project is expected to produce 13 million tons of LNG per year. Key organizations involved include TotalEnergies and Eni, with CEO Patrick Pouyanné visiting Maputo to coordinate with President Filipe Nyusi. The local communities in Palma and Mocímboa da Praia will benefit from development programs.
---------------------------------- RESPONSE ------------------------------------
{"detected_language": "en", "summary_en": "TotalEnergies is resuming its Liquefied Natural Gas (LNG) project in Cabo Delgado, Mozambique, following an improvement in security conditions. The project is projected to yield 13 million tons of LNG annually. Key entities involved are TotalEnergies and Eni, with TotalEnergies' CEO, Patrick Pouyanné, visiting Maputo to coordinate with President Filipe Nyusi. Local communities in Palma and Mocímboa da Praia are expected to benefit from development programs.", "summary_orig": "TotalEnergies relança o projeto de gás liquefeito (LNG) em Cabo Delgado, Moçambique, após a melhoria das condições de segurança. O projeto deve produzir 13 milhões de toneladas de GNL por ano. As organizações chave envolvidas incluem TotalEnergies e Eni, com o CEO da TotalEnergies, Patrick Pouyanné, visitando Maputo para coordenar com o Presidente Filipe Nyusi. As comunidades locais em Palma e Mocímboa da Praia se beneficiarão de programas de desenvolvimento.", "publisher_metadata": {"author": null, "publisher": "substack.com", "platform": "Substack", "date": null}, "entities": [{"raw_name": "TotalEnergies", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Eni", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Patrick Pouyanné", "entity_type": "PERSON"}, {"raw_name": "Filipe Nyusi", "entity_type": "PERSON"}, {"raw_name": "Cabo Delgado", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "Palma", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "Mocímboa da Praia", "entity_type": "GPE"}], "topics": ["Energy", "LNG", "Exploration", "Security", "Development"], "themes": ["Energy Development", "International Investment", "Security Concerns", "Community Benefit"], "keywords": ["LNG", "Mozambique", "Cabo Delgado", "TotalEnergies", "Eni", "Security", "Development"], "subscription_marketing": false}
================================================================================

================================================================================
TIMESTAMP: 2026-05-21 15:12:37
PROVIDER:  ollama
MODEL:     gemma4:e2b
SYSTEM PROMPT:
You are an expert multilingual narrative analyst.
Analyze the provided text and return a JSON object with the following fields:
- "detected_language": The ISO 639-1 code of the source language (e.g. "en", "fr", "pt", "sw", "zu", etc.).
- "summary_en": A detailed English summary capturing key narrative arguments, actors, and nuance.
- "summary_orig": A summary in the original language preserving native idioms and rhetorical style.
- "publisher_metadata": An object with "author" (the writer, or null), "publisher" (publication name, or null), "platform" (e.g. "Substack", "Ghost", "Telegram", "RSS", or null), and "date" (YYYY-MM-DD format, or null).
- "entities": A list of extracted entities, each being an object with "raw_name" (the name of the person, organization, acronym, or region as written) and "entity_type" (must be one of: "PERSON", "ORG", "GPE", "LOC"). Extract acronyms like 'UN', 'SARS', 'SADC' as ORG.
- "topics": A list of up to 5 main general topic labels (e.g. ["Oil & Gas", "Governance"]).
- "themes": A list of core narrative themes/stances (e.g. ["Anti-Colonial Rhetoric", "Economic Protectionism"]).
- "keywords": A list of 5-10 key descriptive words.
- "subscription_marketing": A boolean value (true/false) indicating if this is purely promotional/marketing spam/sign-up page or a paywall placeholder instead of actual editorial content.

Your output MUST be a valid JSON object. Do not wrap it in markdown block quotes (e.g. do not use ```json) or add any leading/trailing commentary. Return ONLY the raw JSON string.
------------------------------------ PROMPT ------------------------------------
TITLE: Transition énergétique en Afrique de l'Ouest : La Cedeao soutient le solaire
SENDER/SOURCE: contact@cedeao.int
CONTENT:
La CEDEAO (Communauté Économique des États de l'Afrique de l'Ouest) a annoncé un nouveau fonds de 500 millions de dollars pour soutenir le développement de projets solaires hors réseau au Sénégal et au Mali. Le commissaire à l'énergie de la CEDEAO, Sékou Sangaré, a précisé que la Banque Ouest Africaine de Développement (BOAD) et la Banque mondiale codirigent l'initiative. Le but est de réduire la dépendance au charbon et de favoriser l'électrification rurale.
---------------------------------- RESPONSE ------------------------------------
{
"detected_language": "fr",
"summary_en": "The ECOWAS (Economic Community of West African States) has announced a new $500 million fund to support the development of off-grid solar projects in Senegal and Mali. The initiative is co-led by the West African Development Bank (BOAD) and the World Bank. The goal of the funding is to reduce dependence on coal and promote rural electrification.",
"summary_orig": "La CEDEAO (Communauté Économique des États de l'Afrique de l'Ouest) a annoncé un nouveau fonds de 500 millions de dollars pour soutenir le développement de projets solaires hors réseau au Sénégal et au Mali. Le commissaire à l'énergie de la CEDEAO, Sékou Sangaré, a précisé que la Banque Ouest Africaine de Développement (BOAD) et la Banque mondiale codirigent l'initiative. Le but est de réduire la dépendance au charbon et de favoriser l'électrification rurale.",
"publisher_metadata": {
"author": null,
"publisher": "CEDEAO",
"platform": null,
"date": null
},
"entities": [
{
"raw_name": "CEDEAO",
"entity_type": "ORG"
},
{
"raw_name": "Sékou Sangaré",
"entity_type": "PERSON"
},
{
"raw_name": "BOAD",
"entity_type": "ORG"
},
{
"raw_name": "Banque mondiale",
"entity_type": "ORG"
},
{
"raw_name": "Sénégal",
"entity_type": "GPE"
},
{
"raw_name": "Mali",
"entity_type": "GPE"
}
],
"topics": [
"Energy",
"Renewable Energy",
"Development Finance",
"Rural Electrification",
"West Africa"
],
"themes": [
"Energy Transition",
"Sustainable Development",
"Decentralization",
"Climate Mitigation"
],
"keywords": [
"Solaire",
"CEDEAO",
"Sénégal",
"Mali",
"Fonds",
"Électrification rurale",
"BOAD"
],
"subscription_marketing": false
}
================================================================================

================================================================================
TIMESTAMP: 2026-05-21 15:12:54
PROVIDER:  ollama
MODEL:     gemma4:e2b
SYSTEM PROMPT:
You are an expert multilingual narrative analyst.
Analyze the provided text and return a JSON object with the following fields:
- "detected_language": The ISO 639-1 code of the source language (e.g. "en", "fr", "pt", "sw", "zu", etc.).
- "summary_en": A detailed English summary capturing key narrative arguments, actors, and nuance.
- "summary_orig": A summary in the original language preserving native idioms and rhetorical style.
- "publisher_metadata": An object with "author" (the writer, or null), "publisher" (publication name, or null), "platform" (e.g. "Substack", "Ghost", "Telegram", "RSS", or null), and "date" (YYYY-MM-DD format, or null).
- "entities": A list of extracted entities, each being an object with "raw_name" (the name of the person, organization, acronym, or region as written) and "entity_type" (must be one of: "PERSON", "ORG", "GPE", "LOC"). Extract acronyms like 'UN', 'SARS', 'SADC' as ORG.
- "topics": A list of up to 5 main general topic labels (e.g. ["Oil & Gas", "Governance"]).
- "themes": A list of core narrative themes/stances (e.g. ["Anti-Colonial Rhetoric", "Economic Protectionism"]).
- "keywords": A list of 5-10 key descriptive words.
- "subscription_marketing": A boolean value (true/false) indicating if this is purely promotional/marketing spam/sign-up page or a paywall placeholder instead of actual editorial content.

Your output MUST be a valid JSON object. Do not wrap it in markdown block quotes (e.g. do not use ```json) or add any leading/trailing commentary. Return ONLY the raw JSON string.
------------------------------------ PROMPT ------------------------------------
TITLE: Angola avança com novos projetos de energia solar em Benguela
SENDER/SOURCE: info@jornaldeangola.ao
CONTENT:
O governo de Angola, representado pelo Ministério da Energia e Águas, assinou um acordo de financiamento com a empresa alemã GAUFF Engineering para construir três centrais solares fotovoltaicas na província de Benguela. O ministro João Baptista Borges destacou que a infraestrutura beneficiará mais de 200 mil famílias e ajudará o país a diversificar a sua matriz energética nacional, reduzindo o consumo de gasóleo.
---------------------------------- RESPONSE ------------------------------------
{"detected_language": "pt", "summary_en": "The government of Angola, represented by the Ministry of Energy and Waters, has signed a financing agreement with the German company GAUFF Engineering to build three photovoltaic solar power plants in the Benguela province. Minister João Baptista Borges highlighted that this infrastructure will benefit more than 200,000 families and help the country diversify its national energy matrix by reducing the consumption of diesel.", "summary_orig": "O governo de Angola, representado pelo Ministério da Energia e Águas, assinou um acordo de financiamento com a empresa alemã GAUFF Engineering para construir três centrais solares fotovoltaicas na província de Benguela. O ministro João Baptista Borges destacou que a infraestrutura beneficiará mais de 200 mil famílias e ajudará o país a diversificar a sua matriz energética nacional, reduzindo o consumo de gasóleo.", "publisher_metadata": {"author": null, "publisher": "jornaldeangola.ao", "platform": null, "date": null}, "entities": [{"raw_name": "Angola", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "Ministério da Energia e Águas", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "GAUFF Engineering", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "João Baptista Borges", "entity_type": "PERSON"}, {"raw_name": "Benguela", "entity_type": "GPE"}], "topics": ["Energy", "Infrastructure", "Renewable Energy", "Finance", "Development"], "themes": ["Energy Diversification", "Infrastructure Development", "International Cooperation"], "keywords": ["solar energy", "Angola", "Benguela", "financing", "renewable", "energy matrix", "diversification"], "subscription_marketing": false}
================================================================================

================================================================================
TIMESTAMP: 2026-05-21 15:13:59
PROVIDER:  ollama
MODEL:     gemma4:e2b
SYSTEM PROMPT:
You are an expert multilingual narrative analyst.
Analyze the provided text and return a JSON object with the following fields:
- "detected_language": The ISO 639-1 code of the source language (e.g. "en", "fr", "pt", "sw", "zu", etc.).
- "summary_en": A detailed English summary capturing key narrative arguments, actors, and nuance.
- "summary_orig": A summary in the original language preserving native idioms and rhetorical style.
- "publisher_metadata": An object with "author" (the writer, or null), "publisher" (publication name, or null), "platform" (e.g. "Substack", "Ghost", "Telegram", "RSS", or null), and "date" (YYYY-MM-DD format, or null).
- "entities": A list of extracted entities, each being an object with "raw_name" (the name of the person, organization, acronym, or region as written) and "entity_type" (must be one of: "PERSON", "ORG", "GPE", "LOC"). Extract acronyms like 'UN', 'SARS', 'SADC' as ORG.
- "topics": A list of up to 5 main general topic labels (e.g. ["Oil & Gas", "Governance"]).
- "themes": A list of core narrative themes/stances (e.g. ["Anti-Colonial Rhetoric", "Economic Protectionism"]).
- "keywords": A list of 5-10 key descriptive words.
- "subscription_marketing": A boolean value (true/false) indicating if this is purely promotional/marketing spam/sign-up page or a paywall placeholder instead of actual editorial content.

Your output MUST be a valid JSON object. Do not wrap it in markdown block quotes (e.g. do not use ```json) or add any leading/trailing commentary. Return ONLY the raw JSON string.
------------------------------------ PROMPT ------------------------------------
TITLE: TotalEnergies advances LNG exploration in Mozambique's Cabo Delgado
SENDER/SOURCE: energy-insights@substack.com
CONTENT:
TotalEnergies is restarting its liquefied natural gas (LNG) project in Cabo Delgado, Mozambique, after security conditions improved. The project is expected to produce 13 million tons of LNG per year. Key organizations involved include TotalEnergies and Eni, with CEO Patrick Pouyanné visiting Maputo to coordinate with President Filipe Nyusi. The local communities in Palma and Mocímboa da Praia will benefit from development programs.
---------------------------------- RESPONSE ------------------------------------
{
  "detected_language": "en",
  "summary_en": "TotalEnergies is resuming its Liquefied Natural Gas (LNG) project in Cabo Delgado, Mozambique, following an improvement in security conditions. The project is projected to yield 13 million tons of LNG annually. Key stakeholders include TotalEnergies and Eni. The CEO of TotalEnergies, Patrick Pouyanné, visited Maputo to coordinate with President Filipe Nyusi, and local communities in Palma and Mocímboa da Praia are expected to benefit from development programs.",
  "summary_orig": "TotalEnergies está retomando seu projeto de gás natural liquefeito (GNL) em Cabo Delgado, Moçambique, após a melhoria das condições de segurança. O projeto deve produzir 13 milhões de toneladas de GNL por ano. As principais organizações envolvidas incluem TotalEnergies e Eni, com o CEO Patrick Pouyanné visitando Maputo para coordenar com o Presidente Filipe Nyusi. As comunidades locais em Palma e Mocímboa da Praia se beneficiarão de programas de desenvolvimento.",
  "publisher_metadata": {
    "author": null,
    "publisher": "substack.com",
    "platform": "Substack",
    "date": null
  },
  "entities": [
    {
      "raw_name": "TotalEnergies",
      "entity_type": "ORG"
    },
    {
      "raw_name": "LNG",
      "entity_type": "ORG"
    },
    {
      "raw_name": "Mozambique",
      "entity_type": "GPE"
    },
    {
      "raw_name": "Cabo Delgado",
      "entity_type": "GPE"
    },
    {
      "raw_name": "Eni",
      "entity_type": "ORG"
    },
    {
      "raw_name": "Patrick Pouyanné",
      "entity_type": "PERSON"
    },
    {
      "raw_name": "Filipe Nyusi",
      "entity_type": "PERSON"
    },
    {
      "raw_name": "Palma",
      "entity_type": "GPE"
    },
    {
      "raw_name": "Mocímboa da Praia",
      "entity_type": "GPE"
    }
  ],
  "topics": [
    "Energy"
  ],
  "themes": [
    "Energy Development",
    "Security",
    "Community Development"
  ],
  "keywords": [
    "LNG",
    "Mozambique",
    "Cabo Delgado",
    "TotalEnergies",
    "Eni",
    "Exploration",
    "Security"
  ],
  "subscription_marketing": false
}
================================================================================

================================================================================
TIMESTAMP: 2026-05-21 15:14:17
PROVIDER:  ollama
MODEL:     gemma4:e2b
SYSTEM PROMPT:
You are an expert multilingual narrative analyst.
Analyze the provided text and return a JSON object with the following fields:
- "detected_language": The ISO 639-1 code of the source language (e.g. "en", "fr", "pt", "sw", "zu", etc.).
- "summary_en": A detailed English summary capturing key narrative arguments, actors, and nuance.
- "summary_orig": A summary in the original language preserving native idioms and rhetorical style.
- "publisher_metadata": An object with "author" (the writer, or null), "publisher" (publication name, or null), "platform" (e.g. "Substack", "Ghost", "Telegram", "RSS", or null), and "date" (YYYY-MM-DD format, or null).
- "entities": A list of extracted entities, each being an object with "raw_name" (the name of the person, organization, acronym, or region as written) and "entity_type" (must be one of: "PERSON", "ORG", "GPE", "LOC"). Extract acronyms like 'UN', 'SARS', 'SADC' as ORG.
- "topics": A list of up to 5 main general topic labels (e.g. ["Oil & Gas", "Governance"]).
- "themes": A list of core narrative themes/stances (e.g. ["Anti-Colonial Rhetoric", "Economic Protectionism"]).
- "keywords": A list of 5-10 key descriptive words.
- "subscription_marketing": A boolean value (true/false) indicating if this is purely promotional/marketing spam/sign-up page or a paywall placeholder instead of actual editorial content.

Your output MUST be a valid JSON object. Do not wrap it in markdown block quotes (e.g. do not use ```json) or add any leading/trailing commentary. Return ONLY the raw JSON string.
------------------------------------ PROMPT ------------------------------------
TITLE: Transition énergétique en Afrique de l'Ouest : La Cedeao soutient le solaire
SENDER/SOURCE: contact@cedeao.int
CONTENT:
La CEDEAO (Communauté Économique des États de l'Afrique de l'Ouest) a annoncé un nouveau fonds de 500 millions de dollars pour soutenir le développement de projets solaires hors réseau au Sénégal et au Mali. Le commissaire à l'énergie de la CEDEAO, Sékou Sangaré, a précisé que la Banque Ouest Africaine de Développement (BOAD) et la Banque mondiale codirigent l'initiative. Le but est de réduire la dépendance au charbon et de favoriser l'électrification rurale.
---------------------------------- RESPONSE ------------------------------------
{"detected_language": "fr", "summary_en": "The ECOWAS (Economic Community of West African States) has announced a new $500 million fund to support the development of off-grid solar projects in Senegal and Mali. The energy commissioner of ECOWAS, Sékou Sangaré, stated that the West African Development Bank (BOAD) and the World Bank are co-directing the initiative. The goal is to reduce dependence on coal and promote rural electrification.", "summary_orig": "La CEDEAO (Communauté Économique des États de l'Afrique de l'Ouest) a annoncé un nouveau fonds de 500 millions de dollars pour soutenir le développement de projets solaires hors réseau au Sénégal et au Mali. Le commissaire à l'énergie de la CEDEAO, Sékou Sangaré, a précisé que la Banque Ouest Africaine de Développement (BOAD) et la Banque mondiale codirigent l'initiative. Le but est de réduire la dépendance au charbon et de favoriser l'électrification rurale.", "publisher_metadata": {"author": null, "publisher": "cedeao.int", "platform": null, "date": null}, "entities": [{"raw_name": "CEDEAO", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Sékou Sangaré", "entity_type": "PERSON"}, {"raw_name": "BOAD", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Banque mondiale", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Sénégal", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "Mali", "entity_type": "GPE"}], "topics": ["Energy", "Finance", "Development", "Renewable Energy", "Africa"], "themes": ["Energy Transition", "Rural Electrification", "Climate Change Mitigation"], "keywords": ["Solar", "ECOWAS", "Senegal", "Mali", "Funding", "Electrification", "Coal"], "subscription_marketing": false}
================================================================================

================================================================================
TIMESTAMP: 2026-05-21 15:14:35
PROVIDER:  ollama
MODEL:     gemma4:e2b
SYSTEM PROMPT:
You are an expert multilingual narrative analyst.
Analyze the provided text and return a JSON object with the following fields:
- "detected_language": The ISO 639-1 code of the source language (e.g. "en", "fr", "pt", "sw", "zu", etc.).
- "summary_en": A detailed English summary capturing key narrative arguments, actors, and nuance.
- "summary_orig": A summary in the original language preserving native idioms and rhetorical style.
- "publisher_metadata": An object with "author" (the writer, or null), "publisher" (publication name, or null), "platform" (e.g. "Substack", "Ghost", "Telegram", "RSS", or null), and "date" (YYYY-MM-DD format, or null).
- "entities": A list of extracted entities, each being an object with "raw_name" (the name of the person, organization, acronym, or region as written) and "entity_type" (must be one of: "PERSON", "ORG", "GPE", "LOC"). Extract acronyms like 'UN', 'SARS', 'SADC' as ORG.
- "topics": A list of up to 5 main general topic labels (e.g. ["Oil & Gas", "Governance"]).
- "themes": A list of core narrative themes/stances (e.g. ["Anti-Colonial Rhetoric", "Economic Protectionism"]).
- "keywords": A list of 5-10 key descriptive words.
- "subscription_marketing": A boolean value (true/false) indicating if this is purely promotional/marketing spam/sign-up page or a paywall placeholder instead of actual editorial content.

Your output MUST be a valid JSON object. Do not wrap it in markdown block quotes (e.g. do not use ```json) or add any leading/trailing commentary. Return ONLY the raw JSON string.
------------------------------------ PROMPT ------------------------------------
TITLE: Angola avança com novos projetos de energia solar em Benguela
SENDER/SOURCE: info@jornaldeangola.ao
CONTENT:
O governo de Angola, representado pelo Ministério da Energia e Águas, assinou um acordo de financiamento com a empresa alemã GAUFF Engineering para construir três centrais solares fotovoltaicas na província de Benguela. O ministro João Baptista Borges destacou que a infraestrutura beneficiará mais de 200 mil famílias e ajudará o país a diversificar a sua matriz energética nacional, reduzindo o consumo de gasóleo.
---------------------------------- RESPONSE ------------------------------------
{"detected_language": "pt", "summary_en": "The government of Angola, represented by the Ministry of Energy and Water, signed a financing agreement with the German company GAUFF Engineering to build three photovoltaic solar power plants in the Benguela province. Minister João Baptista Borges highlighted that this infrastructure will benefit over 200,000 families and help the country diversify its national energy matrix by reducing the consumption of diesel.", "summary_orig": "O governo de Angola, representado pelo Ministério da Energia e Águas, assinou um acordo de financiamento com a empresa alemã GAUFF Engineering para construir três centrais solares fotovoltaicas na província de Benguela. O ministro João Baptista Borges destacou que a infraestrutura beneficiará mais de 200 mil famílias e ajudará o país a diversificar a sua matriz energética nacional, reduzindo o consumo de gasóleo.", "publisher_metadata": {"author": null, "publisher": "jornaldeangola.ao", "platform": null, "date": null}, "entities": [{"raw_name": "Angola", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "GAUFF Engineering", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "João Baptista Borges", "entity_type": "PERSON"}, {"raw_name": "Benguela", "entity_type": "GPE"}], "topics": ["Energy", "Infrastructure", "Renewable Energy", "Finance"], "themes": ["Energy Diversification", "Infrastructure Development", "International Cooperation"], "keywords": ["solar energy", "Angola", "Benguela", "financing", "renewable", "energy matrix"], "subscription_marketing": false}
================================================================================

================================================================================
TIMESTAMP: 2026-05-21 15:45:18
PROVIDER:  ollama
MODEL:     gemma4:e2b
SYSTEM PROMPT:
You are an expert multilingual narrative analyst.
Analyze the provided text and return a JSON object with the following fields:
- "detected_language": The ISO 639-1 code of the source language (e.g. "en", "fr", "pt", "sw", "zu", etc.).
- "summary_en": A detailed English summary capturing key narrative arguments, actors, and nuance.
- "summary_orig": A summary in the original language preserving native idioms and rhetorical style.
- "publisher_metadata": An object with "author" (the writer, or null), "publisher" (publication name, or null), "platform" (e.g. "Substack", "Ghost", "Telegram", "RSS", or null), and "date" (YYYY-MM-DD format, or null).
- "entities": A list of extracted entities, each being an object with "raw_name" (the name of the person, organization, acronym, or region as written) and "entity_type" (must be one of: "PERSON", "ORG", "GPE", "LOC"). Extract acronyms like 'UN', 'SARS', 'SADC' as ORG.
- "topics": A list of up to 5 main general topic labels (e.g. ["Oil & Gas", "Governance"]).
- "themes": A list of core narrative themes/stances (e.g. ["Anti-Colonial Rhetoric", "Economic Protectionism"]).
- "keywords": A list of 5-10 key descriptive words.
- "subscription_marketing": A boolean value (true/false) indicating if this is purely promotional/marketing spam/sign-up page or a paywall placeholder instead of actual editorial content.

Your output MUST be a valid JSON object. Do not wrap it in markdown block quotes (e.g. do not use ```json) or add any leading/trailing commentary. Return ONLY the raw JSON string.
------------------------------------ PROMPT ------------------------------------
TITLE: TotalEnergies advances LNG exploration in Mozambique's Cabo Delgado
SENDER/SOURCE: energy-insights@substack.com
CONTENT:
TotalEnergies is restarting its liquefied natural gas (LNG) project in Cabo Delgado, Mozambique, after security conditions improved. The project is expected to produce 13 million tons of LNG per year. Key organizations involved include TotalEnergies and Eni, with CEO Patrick Pouyanné visiting Maputo to coordinate with President Filipe Nyusi. The local communities in Palma and Mocímboa da Praia will benefit from development programs.
---------------------------------- RESPONSE ------------------------------------
{"detected_language": "en", "summary_en": "TotalEnergies is resuming its Liquefied Natural Gas (LNG) project in Cabo Delgado, Mozambique, following an improvement in security conditions. The project is projected to yield 13 million tons of LNG annually. Key entities involved are TotalEnergies and Eni, and CEO Patrick Pouyanné visited Maputo to coordinate with President Filipe Nyusi. Local communities in Palma and Mocímboa da Praia are expected to benefit from development programs.", "summary_orig": "TotalEnergies está reiniciando seu projeto de gás natural liquefeito (GNL) em Cabo Delgado, Moçambique, após as condições de segurança terem melhorado. O projeto deve produzir 13 milhões de toneladas de GNL por ano. As principais organizações envolvidas incluem TotalEnergies e Eni, com o CEO Patrick Pouyanné visitando Maputo para coordenar com o Presidente Filipe Nyusi. As comunidades locais em Palma e Mocímboa da Praia se beneficiarão de programas de desenvolvimento.", "publisher_metadata": {"author": null, "publisher": "energy-insights@substack.com", "platform": "Substack", "date": null}, "entities": [{"raw_name": "TotalEnergies", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Eni", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Patrick Pouyanné", "entity_type": "PERSON"}, {"raw_name": "Filipe Nyusi", "entity_type": "PERSON"}, {"raw_name": "Cabo Delgado", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "Maputo", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "Palma", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "Mocímboa da Praia", "entity_type": "GPE"}], "topics": ["Energy", "LNG", "Mining & Energy", "Infrastructure", "Development"], "themes": ["Energy Exploration", "Security Context", "International Collaboration", "Community Development"], "keywords": ["LNG", "Mozambique", "Cabo Delgado", "TotalEnergies", "Eni", "Security", "Development", "Gas"], "subscription_marketing": false}
================================================================================

================================================================================
TIMESTAMP: 2026-05-21 15:45:40
PROVIDER:  ollama
MODEL:     gemma4:e2b
SYSTEM PROMPT:
You are an expert multilingual narrative analyst.
Analyze the provided text and return a JSON object with the following fields:
- "detected_language": The ISO 639-1 code of the source language (e.g. "en", "fr", "pt", "sw", "zu", etc.).
- "summary_en": A detailed English summary capturing key narrative arguments, actors, and nuance.
- "summary_orig": A summary in the original language preserving native idioms and rhetorical style.
- "publisher_metadata": An object with "author" (the writer, or null), "publisher" (publication name, or null), "platform" (e.g. "Substack", "Ghost", "Telegram", "RSS", or null), and "date" (YYYY-MM-DD format, or null).
- "entities": A list of extracted entities, each being an object with "raw_name" (the name of the person, organization, acronym, or region as written) and "entity_type" (must be one of: "PERSON", "ORG", "GPE", "LOC"). Extract acronyms like 'UN', 'SARS', 'SADC' as ORG.
- "topics": A list of up to 5 main general topic labels (e.g. ["Oil & Gas", "Governance"]).
- "themes": A list of core narrative themes/stances (e.g. ["Anti-Colonial Rhetoric", "Economic Protectionism"]).
- "keywords": A list of 5-10 key descriptive words.
- "subscription_marketing": A boolean value (true/false) indicating if this is purely promotional/marketing spam/sign-up page or a paywall placeholder instead of actual editorial content.

Your output MUST be a valid JSON object. Do not wrap it in markdown block quotes (e.g. do not use ```json) or add any leading/trailing commentary. Return ONLY the raw JSON string.
------------------------------------ PROMPT ------------------------------------
TITLE: Transition énergétique en Afrique de l'Ouest : La Cedeao soutient le solaire
SENDER/SOURCE: contact@cedeao.int
CONTENT:
La CEDEAO (Communauté Économique des États de l'Afrique de l'Ouest) a annoncé un nouveau fonds de 500 millions de dollars pour soutenir le développement de projets solaires hors réseau au Sénégal et au Mali. Le commissaire à l'énergie de la CEDEAO, Sékou Sangaré, a précisé que la Banque Ouest Africaine de Développement (BOAD) et la Banque mondiale codirigent l'initiative. Le but est de réduire la dépendance au charbon et de favoriser l'électrification rurale.
---------------------------------- RESPONSE ------------------------------------
{
  "detected_language": "fr",
  "summary_en": "The ECOWAS (Economic Community of West African States) has announced a new $500 million fund to support the development of off-grid solar projects in Senegal and Mali. The initiative is co-led by the West African Development Bank (BOAD) and the World Bank. The goal of the fund is to reduce dependence on coal and promote rural electrification.",
  "summary_orig": "La CEDEAO (Communauté Économique des États de l'Afrique de l'Ouest) a annoncé un nouveau fonds de 500 millions de dollars pour soutenir le développement de projets solaires hors réseau au Sénégal et au Mali. Le commissaire à l'énergie de la CEDEAO, Sékou Sangaré, a précisé que la Banque Ouest Africaine de Développement (BOAD) et la Banque mondiale codirigent l'initiative. Le but est de réduire la dépendance au charbon et de favoriser l'électrification rurale.",
  "publisher_metadata": {
    "author": null,
    "publisher": "cedeao.int",
    "platform": null,
    "date": null
  },
  "entities": [
    {
      "raw_name": "CEDEAO",
      "entity_type": "ORG"
    },
    {
      "raw_name": "Sékou Sangaré",
      "entity_type": "PERSON"
    },
    {
      "raw_name": "BOAD",
      "entity_type": "ORG"
    },
    {
      "raw_name": "Banque mondiale",
      "entity_type": "ORG"
    },
    {
      "raw_name": "Sénégal",
      "entity_type": "GPE"
    },
    {
      "raw_name": "Mali",
      "entity_type": "GPE"
    }
  ],
  "topics": [
    "Energy",
    "Finance",
    "Development",
    "Renewable Energy",
    "Rural Electrification"
  ],
  "themes": [
    "Energy Transition",
    "Climate Mitigation",
    "Infrastructure Development",
    "Regional Cooperation"
  ],
  "keywords": [
    "Solaire",
    "CEDEAO",
    "Afrique de l'Ouest",
    "Financement",
    "Électrification rurale"
  ],
  "subscription_marketing": false
}
================================================================================

================================================================================
TIMESTAMP: 2026-05-21 15:45:58
PROVIDER:  ollama
MODEL:     gemma4:e2b
SYSTEM PROMPT:
You are an expert multilingual narrative analyst.
Analyze the provided text and return a JSON object with the following fields:
- "detected_language": The ISO 639-1 code of the source language (e.g. "en", "fr", "pt", "sw", "zu", etc.).
- "summary_en": A detailed English summary capturing key narrative arguments, actors, and nuance.
- "summary_orig": A summary in the original language preserving native idioms and rhetorical style.
- "publisher_metadata": An object with "author" (the writer, or null), "publisher" (publication name, or null), "platform" (e.g. "Substack", "Ghost", "Telegram", "RSS", or null), and "date" (YYYY-MM-DD format, or null).
- "entities": A list of extracted entities, each being an object with "raw_name" (the name of the person, organization, acronym, or region as written) and "entity_type" (must be one of: "PERSON", "ORG", "GPE", "LOC"). Extract acronyms like 'UN', 'SARS', 'SADC' as ORG.
- "topics": A list of up to 5 main general topic labels (e.g. ["Oil & Gas", "Governance"]).
- "themes": A list of core narrative themes/stances (e.g. ["Anti-Colonial Rhetoric", "Economic Protectionism"]).
- "keywords": A list of 5-10 key descriptive words.
- "subscription_marketing": A boolean value (true/false) indicating if this is purely promotional/marketing spam/sign-up page or a paywall placeholder instead of actual editorial content.

Your output MUST be a valid JSON object. Do not wrap it in markdown block quotes (e.g. do not use ```json) or add any leading/trailing commentary. Return ONLY the raw JSON string.
------------------------------------ PROMPT ------------------------------------
TITLE: Angola avança com novos projetos de energia solar em Benguela
SENDER/SOURCE: info@jornaldeangola.ao
CONTENT:
O governo de Angola, representado pelo Ministério da Energia e Águas, assinou um acordo de financiamento com a empresa alemã GAUFF Engineering para construir três centrais solares fotovoltaicas na província de Benguela. O ministro João Baptista Borges destacou que a infraestrutura beneficiará mais de 200 mil famílias e ajudará o país a diversificar a sua matriz energética nacional, reduzindo o consumo de gasóleo.
---------------------------------- RESPONSE ------------------------------------
{"detected_language": "pt", "summary_en": "The government of Angola, represented by the Ministry of Energy and Waters, has signed a financing agreement with the German company GAUFF Engineering to build three photovoltaic solar power plants in the province of Benguela. Minister João Baptista Borges highlighted that this infrastructure will benefit over 200,000 families and help the country diversify its national energy matrix by reducing the consumption of diesel.", "summary_orig": "O governo de Angola, representado pelo Ministério da Energia e Águas, assinou um acordo de financiamento com a empresa alemã GAUFF Engineering para construir três centrais solares fotovoltaicas na província de Benguela. O ministro João Baptista Borges destacou que a infraestrutura beneficiará mais de 200 mil famílias e ajudará o país a diversificar a sua matriz energética nacional, reduzindo o consumo de gasóleo.", "publisher_metadata": {"author": null, "publisher": "jornaldeangola.ao", "platform": null, "date": null}, "entities": [{"raw_name": "Angola", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "AU", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "GAUFF Engineering", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "João Baptista Borges", "entity_type": "PERSON"}, {"raw_name": "Benguela", "entity_type": "GPE"}], "topics": ["Energy", "Infrastructure", "Finance", "Renewable Energy", "Development"], "themes": ["Energy Diversification", "Infrastructure Development", "International Cooperation", "Sustainable Energy"], "keywords": ["Angola", "energia solar", "Benguela", "financiamento", "GAUFF Engineering", "matriz energética"], "subscription_marketing": false}
================================================================================

================================================================================
TIMESTAMP: 2026-05-21 15:47:17
PROVIDER:  ollama
MODEL:     gemma4:e2b
SYSTEM PROMPT:
You are an expert multilingual narrative analyst.
Analyze the provided text and return a JSON object with the following fields:
- "detected_language": The ISO 639-1 code of the source language (e.g. "en", "fr", "pt", "sw", "zu", etc.).
- "summary_en": A detailed English summary capturing key narrative arguments, actors, and nuance.
- "summary_orig": A summary in the original language preserving native idioms and rhetorical style.
- "publisher_metadata": An object with "author" (the writer, or null), "publisher" (publication name, or null), "platform" (e.g. "Substack", "Ghost", "Telegram", "RSS", or null), and "date" (YYYY-MM-DD format, or null).
- "entities": A list of extracted entities, each being an object with "raw_name" (the name of the person, organization, acronym, or region as written) and "entity_type" (must be one of: "PERSON", "ORG", "GPE", "LOC"). Extract acronyms like 'UN', 'SARS', 'SADC' as ORG.
- "topics": A list of up to 5 main general topic labels (e.g. ["Oil & Gas", "Governance"]).
- "themes": A list of core narrative themes/stances (e.g. ["Anti-Colonial Rhetoric", "Economic Protectionism"]).
- "keywords": A list of 5-10 key descriptive words.
- "subscription_marketing": A boolean value (true/false) indicating if this is purely promotional/marketing spam/sign-up page or a paywall placeholder instead of actual editorial content.

Your output MUST be a valid JSON object. Do not wrap it in markdown block quotes (e.g. do not use ```json) or add any leading/trailing commentary. Return ONLY the raw JSON string.
------------------------------------ PROMPT ------------------------------------
TITLE: TotalEnergies advances LNG exploration in Mozambique's Cabo Delgado
SENDER/SOURCE: energy-insights@substack.com
CONTENT:
TotalEnergies is restarting its liquefied natural gas (LNG) project in Cabo Delgado, Mozambique, after security conditions improved. The project is expected to produce 13 million tons of LNG per year. Key organizations involved include TotalEnergies and Eni, with CEO Patrick Pouyanné visiting Maputo to coordinate with President Filipe Nyusi. The local communities in Palma and Mocímboa da Praia will benefit from development programs.
---------------------------------- RESPONSE ------------------------------------
{"detected_language": "en", "summary_en": "TotalEnergies is resuming its liquefied natural gas (LNG) project in Cabo Delgado, Mozambique, following an improvement in security conditions. The project is projected to yield 13 million tons of LNG annually. Key entities involved are TotalEnergies and Eni, with CEO Patrick Pouyanné visiting Maputo to coordinate with President Filipe Nyusi. Local communities in Palma and Mocímboa da Praia are expected to benefit from development programs.", "summary_orig": "TotalEnergies est redémarré son projet de gaz naturel liquéfié (GNL) dans le Cabo Delgado, au Mozambique, après que les conditions de sécurité se soient améliorées. Le projet devrait produire 13 millions de tonnes de GNL par an. Les organisations clés impliquées sont TotalEnergies et Eni, avec le PDG Patrick Pouyanné visitant Maputo pour coordonner avec le Président Filipe Nyusi. Les communautés locales à Palma et Mocímboa da Praia bénéficieront de programmes de développement.", "publisher_metadata": {"author": null, "publisher": "Substack", "platform": "Substack", "date": null}, "entities": [{"raw_name": "TotalEnergies", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "LNG", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Cabo Delgado", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "Mozambique", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "Eni", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Patrick Pouyanné", "entity_type": "PERSON"}, {"raw_name": "Filipe Nyusi", "entity_type": "PERSON"}, {"raw_name": "Palma", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "Mocímboa da Praia", "entity_type": "GPE"}], "topics": ["Energy", "LNG", "Exploration", "Development", "Security"], "themes": ["Energy Projects", "International Investment", "Community Development", "Security Negotiations"], "keywords": ["LNG", "Mozambique", "Cabo Delgado", "TotalEnergies", "Eni", "Security", "Development"], "subscription_marketing": false}
================================================================================

================================================================================
TIMESTAMP: 2026-05-21 15:47:36
PROVIDER:  ollama
MODEL:     gemma4:e2b
SYSTEM PROMPT:
You are an expert multilingual narrative analyst.
Analyze the provided text and return a JSON object with the following fields:
- "detected_language": The ISO 639-1 code of the source language (e.g. "en", "fr", "pt", "sw", "zu", etc.).
- "summary_en": A detailed English summary capturing key narrative arguments, actors, and nuance.
- "summary_orig": A summary in the original language preserving native idioms and rhetorical style.
- "publisher_metadata": An object with "author" (the writer, or null), "publisher" (publication name, or null), "platform" (e.g. "Substack", "Ghost", "Telegram", "RSS", or null), and "date" (YYYY-MM-DD format, or null).
- "entities": A list of extracted entities, each being an object with "raw_name" (the name of the person, organization, acronym, or region as written) and "entity_type" (must be one of: "PERSON", "ORG", "GPE", "LOC"). Extract acronyms like 'UN', 'SARS', 'SADC' as ORG.
- "topics": A list of up to 5 main general topic labels (e.g. ["Oil & Gas", "Governance"]).
- "themes": A list of core narrative themes/stances (e.g. ["Anti-Colonial Rhetoric", "Economic Protectionism"]).
- "keywords": A list of 5-10 key descriptive words.
- "subscription_marketing": A boolean value (true/false) indicating if this is purely promotional/marketing spam/sign-up page or a paywall placeholder instead of actual editorial content.

Your output MUST be a valid JSON object. Do not wrap it in markdown block quotes (e.g. do not use ```json) or add any leading/trailing commentary. Return ONLY the raw JSON string.
------------------------------------ PROMPT ------------------------------------
TITLE: Transition énergétique en Afrique de l'Ouest : La Cedeao soutient le solaire
SENDER/SOURCE: contact@cedeao.int
CONTENT:
La CEDEAO (Communauté Économique des États de l'Afrique de l'Ouest) a annoncé un nouveau fonds de 500 millions de dollars pour soutenir le développement de projets solaires hors réseau au Sénégal et au Mali. Le commissaire à l'énergie de la CEDEAO, Sékou Sangaré, a précisé que la Banque Ouest Africaine de Développement (BOAD) et la Banque mondiale codirigent l'initiative. Le but est de réduire la dépendance au charbon et de favoriser l'électrification rurale.
---------------------------------- RESPONSE ------------------------------------
{"detected_language": "fr", "summary_en": "The ECOWAS (Economic Community of West African States) has announced a new $500 million fund to support the development of off-grid solar projects in Senegal and Mali. Sékou Sangaré, the ECOWAS Commissioner for Energy, stated that the West African Development Bank (BOAD) and the World Bank co-lead this initiative. The goal is to reduce dependence on coal and promote rural electrification.", "summary_orig": "La CEDEAO (Communauté Économique des États de l'Afrique de l'Ouest) a annoncé un nouveau fonds de 500 millions de dollars pour soutenir le développement de projets solaires hors réseau au Sénégal et au Mali. Le commissaire à l'énergie de la CEDEAO, Sékou Sangaré, a précisé que la Banque Ouest Africaine de Développement (BOAD) et la Banque mondiale codirigent l'initiative. Le but est de réduire la dépendance au charbon et de favoriser l'électrification rurale.", "publisher_metadata": {"author": null, "publisher": "cedeao.int", "platform": null, "date": null}, "entities": [{"raw_name": "CEDEAO", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Sékou Sangaré", "entity_type": "PERSON"}, {"raw_name": "BOAD", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Banque mondiale", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "Sénégal", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "Mali", "entity_type": "GPE"}], "topics": ["Energy", "Development", "Renewable Energy", "Finance", "Rural Electrification"], "themes": ["Energy Transition", "Renewable Energy Adoption", "Regional Development", "Rural Electrification"], "keywords": ["Solaire", "CEDEAO", "Sénégal", "Mali", "Fonds", "Électrification", "BOAD", "Banque mondiale"], "subscription_marketing": false}
================================================================================

================================================================================
TIMESTAMP: 2026-05-21 15:47:53
PROVIDER:  ollama
MODEL:     gemma4:e2b
SYSTEM PROMPT:
You are an expert multilingual narrative analyst.
Analyze the provided text and return a JSON object with the following fields:
- "detected_language": The ISO 639-1 code of the source language (e.g. "en", "fr", "pt", "sw", "zu", etc.).
- "summary_en": A detailed English summary capturing key narrative arguments, actors, and nuance.
- "summary_orig": A summary in the original language preserving native idioms and rhetorical style.
- "publisher_metadata": An object with "author" (the writer, or null), "publisher" (publication name, or null), "platform" (e.g. "Substack", "Ghost", "Telegram", "RSS", or null), and "date" (YYYY-MM-DD format, or null).
- "entities": A list of extracted entities, each being an object with "raw_name" (the name of the person, organization, acronym, or region as written) and "entity_type" (must be one of: "PERSON", "ORG", "GPE", "LOC"). Extract acronyms like 'UN', 'SARS', 'SADC' as ORG.
- "topics": A list of up to 5 main general topic labels (e.g. ["Oil & Gas", "Governance"]).
- "themes": A list of core narrative themes/stances (e.g. ["Anti-Colonial Rhetoric", "Economic Protectionism"]).
- "keywords": A list of 5-10 key descriptive words.
- "subscription_marketing": A boolean value (true/false) indicating if this is purely promotional/marketing spam/sign-up page or a paywall placeholder instead of actual editorial content.

Your output MUST be a valid JSON object. Do not wrap it in markdown block quotes (e.g. do not use ```json) or add any leading/trailing commentary. Return ONLY the raw JSON string.
------------------------------------ PROMPT ------------------------------------
TITLE: Angola avança com novos projetos de energia solar em Benguela
SENDER/SOURCE: info@jornaldeangola.ao
CONTENT:
O governo de Angola, representado pelo Ministério da Energia e Águas, assinou um acordo de financiamento com a empresa alemã GAUFF Engineering para construir três centrais solares fotovoltaicas na província de Benguela. O ministro João Baptista Borges destacou que a infraestrutura beneficiará mais de 200 mil famílias e ajudará o país a diversificar a sua matriz energética nacional, reduzindo o consumo de gasóleo.
---------------------------------- RESPONSE ------------------------------------
{"detected_language": "pt", "summary_en": "The government of Angola, represented by the Ministry of Energy and Water, signed a financing agreement with the German company GAUFF Engineering to build three photovoltaic solar power plants in the Benguela province. Minister João Baptista Borges highlighted that this infrastructure will benefit over 200,000 families and help the country diversify its national energy matrix by reducing the consumption of diesel.", "summary_orig": "O governo de Angola, representado pelo Ministério da Energia e Águas, assinou um acordo de financiamento com a empresa alemã GAUFF Engineering para construir três centrais solares fotovoltaicas na província de Benguela. O ministro João Baptista Borges destacou que a infraestrutura beneficiará mais de 200 mil famílias e ajudará o país a diversificar a sua matriz energética nacional, reduzindo o consumo de gasóleo.", "publisher_metadata": {"author": null, "publisher": "jornaldeangola.ao", "platform": null, "date": null}, "entities": [{"raw_name": "Angola", "entity_type": "GPE"}, {"raw_name": "GAUFF Engineering", "entity_type": "ORG"}, {"raw_name": "João Baptista Borges", "entity_type": "PERSON"}, {"raw_name": "Benguela", "entity_type": "GPE"}], "topics": ["Energy", "Infrastructure", "Finance", "Renewable Energy", "Development"], "themes": ["Energy Diversification", "Infrastructure Development", "International Cooperation", "Rural Benefit"], "keywords": ["solar energy", "Angola", "Benguela", "financing", "renewable", "energy matrix", "infrastructure"], "subscription_marketing": false}
================================================================================

